Lorenzo Javier Colodro

Software developer

💌 javiercolodro@gmail.com 📞 +54 9358 4392425 👂 Córdoba -Argentina 🕡 Github in Linked In 🤻 Portfolio

ABOUT ME

My experience in aviation has been a significant part of my personal and professional growth for 5 years. In this new stage in programming, I am excited to apply the skills I acquired through an intensive JavaScript Bootcamp. My challenge is to provide valuable contributions to any project I am involved in and meet the needs of the company.

I aim to transition my career and aspirations into the technology sector, combining my programming knowledge with my passion for delivering excellent customer service.

PROJECTS

FullStack Developer - BOX APP ∅

01/2024 - 04/2024

- Delivery Application Project.
- Collaborative Project: 3 months development.
- Agile Methodologies Applied: Scrum, Trello, Daily Stand-up Meetings: Regular briefings to discuss progress, challenges and
- Technologies Applied: React Native (expo to run Android, IOs, and Web), Tailwind, TypeScript, Redux, MongoDB, Next, Docker, Table Plus.

FullStack Developer - House of Dev &

11/2023 - 12/2023

- Develop a real estate application with both Backend and Frontend components, enabling users to browse available properties for rent and sale.
- Collaborative Project: 4 weeks of development.
- Technologies Used: React Vite, Bootstrap, Sass, Sequelize, Node.js, Express, Redux.
- Agile Methodologies Applied: Scrum, Trello, Daily Stand-up Meetings: Regular briefings to discuss progress, challenges, and plan the day's work.
- Demos: Presentations to showcase and detail project advancements.
- GitHub is utilized for collaborative version control, facilitating teamwork and efficient code management.

FullStack Developer - TMDB ∅

12/2023

- Individual Movie Application Project.
- Technologies Applied: React, Bootstrap, CSS, Sequelize, Node.js, Express, and Redux.
- The project focuses on creating a movie application with a seamless user experience. The application enables users to navigate, search, and manage movie-related information.
- GitHub is utilized for version control and collaborative development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML | CSS | SASS | JAVASCRIPT | REACT | SEQUELIZE | NODEJS | POSTGRESQL | REDUX | BOOTSTRAP | GITHUB | POSTMAN | TAILWIND | NEST

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Support in Call Center

11/2021 - 12/2022

- Managing and responding to 30-40 phone calls, chats, and emails daily to ensure optimal customer assistance.
- Providing support and assistance to customers across 34 states in the United States and Central America.

10/2014 - 01/2021 **Cabin Crew**

- I was responsible for the safety and excellent service to customers on 23 domestic flights and 22 international destinations.
- I had the opportunity to supervise 10 regional flights for junior crew members and achieve improved performance.

EDUCATION

JavaScript Bootcamp on Plataforma 5

09/2023

- +1000 hours of coding
- 9 AM to 7 PM schedule
- 7 months intensive
- Pair-programming activities
- Agile methodologies: Scrum, Planning, Daily Stand-up, Review, Demo, and Trello.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- Fluent English